{
    "id": "d3e1b9323bd44af7a83858abc91396df",
    "title": "Active And Passive Voice Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The problem …………………. to the children.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "explained",
                "was explained"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7b082f78f7b64f79a32f6e7fe34843d0"
        },
        {
            "question": "Those pyramids …………………. around 400 AD.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "built",
                "were built"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b22e4912bba74776a7214f3384fd3170"
        },
        {
            "question": "All the trouble ………………… .. by your mother.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has caused",
                "was caused"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c4572346fcd843dabd6088039266abdc"
        },
        {
            "question": "The visitors …………………. a collection of old manuscripts.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "were shown",
                "have shown"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5bdb7680ef284112b8aae9abaef4e4f6"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………. him ten thousand pounds last year.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "lend",
                "lent"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "11cbcef265534b42be26dd3787c983af"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………… of spiders.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "frightened",
                "is frightened"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cf4ddaeccb6844ff8d84c92ddad88b7e"
        },
        {
            "question": "That picture …………………. by my grandmother.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "painted",
                "has painted",
                "was painted"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a043aee9881e4a9fae433325ce8d4385"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………….. by his attitude.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "shocked",
                "was shocked",
                "have shocked"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9c58a284e0e946888ae5f88891ec1ac9"
        },
        {
            "question": "Excuse the mess. The house …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is painting",
                "is painted",
                "is being painted"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9f8aae3308914adda3f0f476f9fd68a3"
        },
        {
            "question": "I knew why I ………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "had chosen",
                "had been chosen"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "82031c9b5921425580550b477c9a8d1a"
        }
    ]
}